

### **Scott Walsh**

Web Developer/ UX Designer / Photographer

Telephone 705-760-2645

Email scmwalsh@gmail.com

Website www.scottwalsh.ca

Located Toronto, ON

### **Profile**

Creating, learning and exploring are my passions. I am an ambitious self-starter with an open-minded attitude which has led me on amazing adventures such as travelling the world and founding my own business. I meet challenges head-on with an approach that demonstrates my ability to exercise creativity when solving problems. I thrive at the intersection where I am able to utilize both my engineering background and creative skills. Photography, development and design allows me to demonstrate my ability to build and problem solve while being able to do what I love everyday.

## **Technical Skills**

Ruby on Rails	••••
HTML	••••
CSS	• • • • •
Javascript	• • • • •
Jquery	• • • • •
GIT	• • • • •
Adobe	

## **Experience**

# Front-End Developer & UX Designer BAM Builder Marketing & Advertising

Present

Responsible for wireframing, UI/UX layouts and building front-end architecture for eBam projects. Developed fully functional responsive websites based on Business Requirements using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and JQuery.

## Co-Founder & Developer, Activate https://activate-app.herokuapp.com/

2015 - Present

2009 - 2011

• Activate is web-based application for people to connect. Create an account, make a new Activity and interact with other Activate users.

## Owner, Scott Walsh Photography 2011 - Present www.scottwwalshphotography.com

Successfully established, own and manage a freelance photography business for 5 years, acquiring a diverse range of commercial clients

#### HIGHLIGHTS

### Coors Social Media Product/Lifestyle Photographer Rethink Communications, Toronto

- Responsible for shooting and editing all photos for Rethink's client,
   Molson Coors, for the Coors Altitude social media channels
- Strategize with the Rethink account team on monthly client briefs in order to establish creative content for the Coors social calendars

# Creative Lead & Social Media Manager Ichiup Beverage Co., Toronto

- Responsible for the planning and execution of all social content for Ichiup's Canadian water brand launch, resulting in the Instagram page growing to +1200 fans
- Worked with the leadership team to create the brand's visual identity,
   shooting +600 photos used in social and print media

#### Photography Contributor Flashstock, Toronto

 Work with large consumer brands to deliver commercial images based on the clients' above-the-line communication needs.: Google Play, Fido, Interac and Nicorette.

## **Education**

TORONTO, ON	2015
UX Design, Bitmaker Labs TORONTO, ON	2015 - 2016

Electrical Engineering, Sir Sanford Fleming